CHRISTIAN MILICEVIC

DEVELOPER & DEVSECOPS

CURRICULUM VITAI

PROFILE



I am a recent IT graduate of the Queensland University of Technology who is commencing a career in software development, programming and cyber security. I supported my university studies with casual employment, focusing on IT, warehousing and mechanics. I have a strong worth ethic and enjoy team-based projects, meeting with people from diverse backgrounds and experiences, and I thrive on challenges that involve multiple responsibilities.

EXPERIENCE

SUNCORP

Software Engineer Cybersecurity/DevSecOps – permanent full-time | Brisbane QLD | Nov 2021 – Present

Suncorp is an Australian based finance and banking company, that is one of Australia's biggest. It is based in Brisbane Queensland and is owned by the Queensland Government. They recently build a new office building in Queen Street to combined the whole team into one building. My responsibilities in this role include:

- Bug fixing and code clean up;
- Automating system platforms for teams to use;
- Solving system platform problems;
- Improving, integrating, maintain and securing any platform features;
- On call roster basis;

GAMELOFT

Quality Assurance (QA) Engineer – permanent full-time | Brisbane QLD | Jun 2021 – Nov 2021

Gameloft is a global publisher of digital and social games for mobile phones. With headquarters in France, it has a presence and partnership network in 148 countries. All games are developed inhouse and the company has the largest development and creation team in the digital games industry. My responsibilities in this role include:

- Querying Cloud database using SQL, Snowflake and documenting working solutions;
- Querying and graphing Snowflake queries into Looker API;
- CI/CD pipeline Jenkins;
- Reporting, reviewing and documenting bugs in Jira;
- Project-based game delivery, including current project, The Oregon Trail Game;
- Utilising iPhone, Mac OS, Apple TV systems as part of project delivery; and
- Participating in team-based meetings and discussions.

CONTACT



Camira, Brisbane, Australia

(PO Box 270 INDOOROOPILLY CENTRE QLD 4068)



0481 335 145



Cmilicevic3@gmail.com



www.christianmilicevic.com (Portfolio)

EDUCATION

GRADUATE CERTIFICATE IN CYBERSECURITY & NETWORKING

Melbourne Institute of Technology, 2021

BACHELOR OF GAMES &
INTERACTIVE ENVIRONMENTS
(SOFTWARE TECHNOLOGIES)

Queensland University of Technology, 2020

DIPLOMA OF DIGITAL
INTERACTIVE GAME DESIGN

Queensland TAFE – Southbank campus, 2017

QUEENSLAND CERTIFICATE OF EDUCATION

John Paul College, Daisy Hill QLD, 2016

ACHIEVEMENTS

SPONSORED STUDY

In 2021, I was awarded a Commonwealth Government grant to undertake postgraduate studies in cyber security through MIT.

A C A D E M I C A C H I E V E M E N T

I was awarded a Bachelor with Distinction upon completion of my studies in IT at QUT in 2020.

CHRISTIAN MILICEVIC

DEVELOPER & DEVSECOPS

CURRICULUM VITAE

EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

FILEMAN

Graduate Solutions Programmer / Support Engineer (Junior Developer) – permanent full-time | Paradise Point QLD | 2021 Feb – Jun 2021

Fileman is an Australian-based business that develops and maintains a Cloud-based file management tool to enable legal corporations to manage the storage and destruction of closed case files. It enables instant location, retrieval and addition to case documents. My main duties in this position included:

- Programming, source control and code quality control;
- Implementing new systems and features;
- Bug fixing and code clean up;
- · Handling tickets from clients (legal professionals); and
- Communicating with other team members and clients.

COLES GROUP LTD (WAREHOUSE DIVISION)

Warehouse Picker -Packer/Loader - Part-time Casual | Forest Lake QLD | Sep 2018 - Sep 2021

Warehouse distribution centre supplying all Coles Supermarkets in the greater

Queensland region and northern New South Wales. Duties included:

- Order selection and packing for store distribution through whole of Queensland and northern NSW;
- Quality control and loss prevention;
- Dangerous goods awareness; and
- Loading pallets to semi-trailers and operation of heavy machinery.

PREVIOUS CASUAL POSITIONS

Goals A+N - IT Relocation Technician — Casual | Geebung QLD | Jan 2018 — Sep 2018

Stadiums QLD — Events Staff — Part-time Casual | Woolloongabba QLD | 2017 — 2020

City Beach Warehouse — Picker/Packer — Part-time Casual | Murrarie QLD | 2017 — 2018

N&D Mechanical Repairs — Mechanic's Assistant — Part-time Casual | Wacol QLD | 2015 — 2017

PERSONAL DATA

CITIZENSHIP

Australian (by birth)

INTERESTS & HOBBIES

- Car enthusiast
- IT enthusiast
- Health & fitness
- International travel
- Snowboarding
- Scuba diving

IT PROGRAMS & LANGUAGES

- AWS
- Jenkins
- · Python, Ansible
- HTML, CSS, JS
- SQL Server, MySQL
- JFrog Xray, JFrog Artifactory
- Fortify
- C# (.NET, ASP.NET, Window Forms)
- · Git, GitHub Desktop, Git Bash
- Jira, Confluence, Bitbucket
- Keepass
- · Atom, Visual Studios
- Unity
- Splunk
- · Snowflake, Looker

REFERENCES

GAMELOFT

Ms M Ingham Former supervisor Contact details upon request

COLES WAREHOUSE

Mr A Henderson Former supervisor Contact details upon request